Trice, Harrison M. Additional Papers /4164
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Mr. Ertner - EAP Interview Schedule, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 61)
- Mr. Ertner - Corporate Staff Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 35, Folder 62)
- Shortened Interview with Dan Ertner, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 63)
- Jerry Cassuto - EAP Interview Schedule, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 64)
- Jerry Cassuto - Corporate Medical Directors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 65)
- Interview with Dr. Jerry Cassuto, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 66)
- Dowdall and Kahn - Corporate Labor Relations Staff Interviews, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 67)
- Unnamed #1 - Corporate Medical Directors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 68)
- Unnamed #2 - Corporate Medical Directors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 69)
- Unnamed #3 - Corporate Medical Directors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 70)
- Doue - Corporate Labor Relations Staff Interview, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 71)
- Interview with Corporate Labor Relations Managers, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 72)
- Interview at Corporate Headquarters - Staff Labor Relations, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 73)
- Interview with unidentified member of labor relations staff at headquarters, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 74)
- Clancy - Corporate Labor Relations Staff Interview, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 75)
- Notes on Interview with Mr. Clancy, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 76)
- Garvey - Corporate Labor Relations Staff Interview, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 77)
- Interview with Ms. Garvey, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 78)
- Miscellaneous Notes on Western Electric and from Visit to Corporate Headquarters, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 79)
- Classification System for Corporate Professional and Administrative Occupations and Western Electric Glossary for Office and Technical Work, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 80)
- Data Summary 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Chapter V: Results and Discussions - no date (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Statistical Tables and Variable Definition - no date (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Tabulation by Location 1974 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Tab le Percentages and Data - no date (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Supervisor Data Summary 1975 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Director Data Summary 1975 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Data Summaries, Tables, Notes 1975 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Statistical Data and Results 1975 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence 1973-1976 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- R.E. Hunt 1975 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Richard Katany 1971-1973 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Jack Stevens (Weekly Reports 6/12/75-8/4/75), 1975 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Janice Beyer Trice 1975 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Verg 1973 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Mona and Jean to Janice Trice, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Pre-Visitation Letter 1974 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Personnel Information Summary Form - no date (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Post-Visit Thank You Correspondence 1974 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Grant 1972-1974 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- Pre-Test Calendars, Memos, and Notes 1973-1975 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- Questionnaire Development 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 22)
- Albany Data Synopsis and Revision - no date (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Post Albany Revisions and Incorporation of Tulane Input 1973, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 24)
- Post Albany #2 1973 (Box 37, Folder 25)
- Albany Pretest - GSA, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 26)
- Atlanta Schedule Comments and Data Synopsis 1973 (Box 37, Folder 27)
- Pre-Atlanta Instruments - no date (Box 37, Folder 28)
- FDA-Atlanta - Spring 1973 (Pretest) (Box 37, Folder 29)
- Atlanta GAO 1973 (Box 37, Folder 30)
- Atlanta HUD - no date (Box 37, Folder 31)
- Atlanta SSA - Pretest 1973 (Box 37, Folder 32)
- Buffalo IRS: Raw Data 1973 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Buffalo IRS: Raw Data 1973 continued (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Post Buffalo #1 and #2 - no date (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Buffalo Pretest 7/25-7/26 - no date (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Buffalo Revisions 1973 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Buffalo Instruments - no date (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Statistical and Miscellaneous Pretest Info 1973-1975 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Organizational Chart - no date (Box 38, Folder 8)
  Organization Charts of various federal agencies and departments
- Federal Personnel Manual System Letter 1971 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Inspectable Installations 1972 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Interview Summaries - no date (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Union Interview/Documentation 1973-1976 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Interview with Union Leaders 1976 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Union Alcohol Policies 1973 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Published Articles 1968-1972 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Published Articles 1967-1974 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Articles and Book Summaries 1965-1973 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Statistical Background 1973 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Background Information 1973-1977 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous Background Information 1968 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Original Test Forms (Box 38, Folder 21)
- Original Tests - Policy Implementation in the Public Sector (Box 38, Folder 22)
- Original Tests continued (Box 38, Folder 23)
- Union Raw Data 1975 (Box 38, Folder 24)
- Director Raw Data - no date (Box 38, Folder 25)
- EEO Functionary Raw Data - no date (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Supervisor Q5 Raw Data - no date (Box 38, Folder 27)
- Alcohol Coordinator Raw Data - no date (Box 38, Folder 28)
- Policy Implementation Raw Data - no date (Box 38, Folder 29)
- Alcohol Policy Coordinator Raw Data - no date (Box 38, Folder 30)
- Alcoholism Coordinator Raw Data - no date (Box 38, Folder 31)
- Alcoholism Coordinator Raw Data - no date continued (Box 38, Folder 32)
- Supervisor Q31 Raw Data - no date (Box 38, Folder 33)
- Supervisor Q25 Raw Data - no date (Box 38, Folder 34)
- Supervisor Q28 Raw Data - no date (Box 38, Folder 35)
- EEO Functionary Raw Data - no date (Box 38, Folder 36)
- Supervisor Q28 Raw Data - no date continued (Box 38, Folder 37)
- EEO Coordinator Raw Data - no date (Box 38, Folder 38)
- Director Raw Data - no date continued (Box 38, Folder 39)
- Supervisor Q31 Raw Data - no date continued (Box 38, Folder 40)
- 1NS Interviews (Box 39, Folder 1)
- 2NS Interviews (Box 39, Folder 2)
- 3NS Interviews (Box 39, Folder 3)
- 4NS Interviews (Box 39, Folder 4)
- 5NS Interviews (Box 39, Folder 5)
- 6NS Interviews (Box 39, Folder 6)
- 7NS Interviews (Box 39, Folder 7)
- 8NS Interviews (Box 39, Folder 8)
- 9NS Interviews (Box 39, Folder 9)
- 10NS Interviews (Box 39, Folder 10)
- 11NS Interviews (Box 39, Folder 11)
- 12NS Interviews (Box 39, Folder 12)
- 13NS Interviews (Box 39, Folder 13)
- 14NS Interviews (Box 39, Folder 14)
- 15NS Interviews (Box 39, Folder 15)
- 16NS Interviews (Box 39, Folder 16)
- 18NS Interviews (Box 39, Folder 17)
- 18NS Interviews (Box 39, Folder 18)
- 19NS Interviews (Box 39, Folder 19)
- 20NS Interviews (Box 40, Folder 1)
- 21NS Interviews (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 22NS Interviews, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- 23NS Interviews (Box 40, Folder 4)
- 24NS Interviews (Box 40, Folder 5)
- 25NS Interviews (Box 40, Folder 6)
- 26NS Interviews (Box 40, Folder 7)
- 27NS Interviews, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- 28NS Interviews (Box 40, Folder 9)
- 29NS Interviews (Box 40, Folder 10)
- 30NS Interviews (Box 40, Folder 11)
- 31NS Interviews (Box 40, Folder 12)
- 32NS Interviews (Box 40, Folder 13)
- 33NS Interviews (Box 40, Folder 14)
- 34NS Interviews (Box 40, Folder 15)
- 35NS Interviews (Box 40, Folder 16)
- 36NS Interviews (Box 40, Folder 17)
- 37NS Interviews (Box 40, Folder 18)
- 38NS Interviews (Box 40, Folder 19)
- 39NS Interviews (Box 40, Folder 20)
- 40NS Interviews (Box 40, Folder 21)
- Trice Director File - Tape Number TU6102 (Box 40.1, Folder 1)
  Computer Tape
- THU Trice Director File - Tape Number U65002 (Box 40.1, Folder 2)
  Computer tape
- Trice EEO Coordinator File - Tape Number TU6272 (Box 40.1, Folder 3)
- Trice ALC Trans File - Tape Number TU6055 (Box 40.1, Folder 4)
- Trice EEO File - Tape Number TU6177 (Box 40.1, Folder 5)
- Trice ALC Coordinator File #2 - Tape Number TU6054 (Box 40.1, Folder 6)
- Trice ALC Coordinator File #1 - Tape Number TU6053 (Box 40.1, Folder 7)
- 41NS Interviews (Box 41, Folder 1)
- 42NS Interviews (Box 41, Folder 2)
- 43NS Interviews (Box 41, Folder 3)
- 44NS Interviews (Box 41, Folder 4)
- 45NS Interviews (Box 41, Folder 5)
- 46NS Interviews (Box 41, Folder 6)
- 47NS Interviews (Box 41, Folder 7)
- 48NS Interviews (Box 41, Folder 8)
- 49NS Interviews, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- 50NS Interviews (Box 41, Folder 10)
- 51NS Interviews (Box 41, Folder 11)
- 52NS Interviews, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- 53NS Interviews (Box 41, Folder 13)
- 54NS Interviews (Box 41, Folder 14)
- 55NS Interviews (Box 41, Folder 15)
- 56NS Interviews (Box 41, Folder 16)
- 57NS Interviews (Box 41, Folder 17)
- 58NS Interviews, 1972-1974 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- 60NS Interviews (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Trice EEO Trans File - Tape Number TU6277 (Box 41.1, Folder 1)
- Trice Structure File - Tape Number TU6191 (Box 41.1, Folder 2)
- Trice Supervisor File - Tape Number TU6134 (Box 41.1, Folder 3)
- Trice ALC Coordinator File - Tape Number TU6101 (Box 41.1, Folder 4)
- Trice Structure File #2 - Tape Number TU6128 (Box 41.1, Folder 5)
- Trice EEO File #2 - Tape Number TU6103 (Box 41.1, Folder 6)
- 63NS Interviews (Box 42, Folder 1)
- 64NS Interviews (Box 42, Folder 2)
- 65NS Interviews (Box 42, Folder 3)
- 66NS Interviews (Box 42, Folder 4)
- 67NS Interviews (Box 42, Folder 5)
- 68NS Interviews (Box 42, Folder 6)
- 69NS Interviews (Box 42, Folder 7)
- 70NS Interviews (Box 42, Folder 8)
- 71NS Interviews, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- 72NS Interviews, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- 73NS Interviews, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- 98NS Interviews (Box 42, Folder 12)
- 98NS Interviews Inappropriates (Box 42, Folder 13)
- 98NS Interviews Inappropriates continued (Box 42, Folder 14)
- 98NS Interviews Inappropriates final (Box 42, Folder 15)
- 99NS Interviews (EEO only), 1975 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- 99S Interviews (Box 42, Folder 17)
- 112NS Interviews, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- 112NS Interviews continued, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- First Series of Recommendations for Change in National Council on Alcoholism (NCA) - Harrison M. Trice (HMT) and Janice Beyer, 1980 (Box 42.1, Folder 1)
- NCA Program Set-up Information, 1980 (Box 42.1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence with Brinkley Smithers regarding NCA feedback, 1980 (Box 42.1, Folder 3)
- Trice and NCA Correspondence, 1980 (Box 42.1, Folder 4)
- NCA Executive Committee Meeting, 1980 (Box 42.1, Folder 5)
  June 13, 1980
- New York - NCA Office Meeting - Including Financials and Notes, 1980 (Box 42.1, Folder 6)
  August 8 and 9, 1980
- Meetings on Affiliates (Box 42.1, Folder 7)
- Pratt - Board Member, 1977 (Box 42.1, Folder 8)
- Jasper and Keith (Box 42.1, Folder 9)
- Peter Hutt (Box 42.1, Folder 10)
- George Marcella (Box 42.1, Folder 11)
- Gordon - Meeting with State Officials, 1980 (Box 42.1, Folder 12)
  May 5, 1980
- NCA Officers Meeting - Miscellaneous Notes; Minutes (Box 42.1, Folder 13)
- Anne Basher (Box 42.1, Folder 14)
- Frank S. (Box 42.1, Folder 15)
- Idaho and Michigan Affiliates (Box 42.1, Folder 16)
- Sheila B. (Box 42.1, Folder 17)
- Dora Goldstein (Box 42.1, Folder 18)
- Mike Ford (Box 42.1, Folder 19)
- Bill Duncan - Notes (Box 42.1, Folder 20)
- Leo Perlis Interview and Toni D'Angelo Interview, 1980 (Box 42.1, Folder 21)
  July 31, 1980
- NCA Board Letter, 1980 (Box 42.1, Folder 22)
- NCA Financial Reports 1978-80, 1978-1980 (Box 42.1, Folder 23)
- NCA Financials, 1979-1981 (Box 42.1, Folder 24)
- Correspondence - Business Against Drunk and Drugged Driving, 1985-1987 (Box 42.1, Folder 25)
- Nurses Association (Box 42.1, Folder 26)
- National Alcoholism Profressional society Questionnaire and Followup, 1979-1980 (Box 42.1, Folder 27)
- National Alcoholism Forum, 1980 (Box 42.1, Folder 28)
  May 1-7, 1980
- NCA Notes (Box 42.1, Folder 29)
- OPC Notes (Box 42.1, Folder 30)
- Handwritten NCA Interview Notes - HMT (Box 42.1, Folder 31)
- Handwritten Notes (continued) - NCA Board Meetings/Problems (Box 42.1, Folder 32)
- NCA Handwritten Notes - HMT (Box 42.1, Folder 33)
- Report of the Cornell Evaluation of Corporate Headquarters Alcoholism Project (CHAP), 1977 (Box 42.1, Folder 34)
  December 31, 1977
- Draft - Final Report - CHAP (Box 42.1, Folder 35)
- Cornell CHAP Evaluation Proposal (Box 42.1, Folder 36)
- Grant Application - Evaluation of New York State Occupational Alcoholism Consultation, 1975 (Box 42.1, Folder 37)
- Draft - Final Report- Evaluating Job-Based Programs for Problem Drinkers (Box 42.1, Folder 38)
- American Institute for Decision Sciences Conference, 1984 (Box 42.1, Folder 39)
  November 5-7, 1984
- St. Louis Bar Association Training Program, 1970 (Box 42.1, Folder 40)
- Perlis and Whitney Post Interviews, 1975-1976 (Box 42.1, Folder 41)
- Working Paper: Alternative to Solomon 4-Way Design (Box 42.1, Folder 42)
- Appendix A: Training Content and Handout Material (Box 42.1, Folder 43)
- Appendix A - Semantic Differentials (Box 42.1, Folder 44)
- Appendix A - Expectations Scale (Box 42.1, Folder 45)
- Outline for Handouts in Training Session #2, 1957-1965 (Box 42.1, Folder 46)
- Outline for Handouts continued, 1957-1965 (Box 42.1, Folder 47)
- General Training Strategy, 1956-1959 (Box 42.1, Folder 48)
- Grant Application - Work Related Stress and Substance Use Among Women, 1978-1980 (Box 42.1, Folder 49)
  Includes Janice Beyer's Social Security Number
- Alcoholism Programs in the Work World - An Historical Perspective - Notes Mona S., 1973 (Box 42.1, Folder 50)
- Grant Application - Prevention Strategies for Working Women Under Stress, 1979-1981 (Box 42.1, Folder 51)
- Janice Beyer Interview Notes, 1980 (Box 42.1, Folder 52)
- Women State Organizations (Box 42.1, Folder 53)
- "Alcohol and Drugs in Airline Operations" by Victoria Frankovich, 1987 (Box 42.1, Folder 54)
- Factors Relating to Relapse in Alcoholic Airline Pilots, 1986 (Box 42.1, Folder 55)
- Alcohol Rehabilitation of Airline Pilots, 1985 (Box 42.1, Folder 56)
- Northwest Airlines v. Airline Pilots Association, 1986-1987 (Box 42.1, Folder 57)
  United States Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia Circuit
- Airline Pilots' Perspective on Alcohol and Drugs in Airline Operations (Box 42.1, Folder 58)
- Bibliography of Alcohol and Drug Court Decisions (Box 42.1, Folder 59)
- Workplace Drug Testing Pamphlets, 1987 (Box 42.1, Folder 60)
- Drug Use Among Workers - Developing Policies and Guidelines, 1974 (Box 42.1, Folder 61)
- Alcohol/Drug-Free Schools in New York State, 1987 (Box 42.1, Folder 62)
- HMT Notes (Box 42.1, Folder 63)
- AFL-CIO Guide - Drug and Alcohol Testing, 1986 (Box 42.1, Folder 64)
- ILR Report (Spring 1986) - Lessons from EAPs and Drug Screening (Box 42.1, Folder 65)
- Bureau of National Affairs (BNA) Report - Alcohol and Drugs in the Workplace, 1986 (Box 42.1, Folder 66)
- Miscellaneous Notes (Box 42.1, Folder 67)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 8-11 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 13-15 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 121-02-01-3 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 121-02-04-5 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 131-03-01-3 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 131-03-04-5 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 131-04-01-3 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 131-04-04-6 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 132-05-01-5 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 132-05-06-9 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 132-05-17-19 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 132-05-20-23 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 132-05-10-13 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 132-05-14-16 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 132-06-01-3 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 132-06-04-7 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 211-07-01-6 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 221-08-01-3 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 231-09-01-3 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 231-09-04-7 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 311-10-01-5 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 311-11-01-3 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 311-11-04-6 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 311-12-01-2 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 311-13-01-4 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 311-14-01-2, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  Interview 311-14-03 is missing
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 311-14-04-5 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 312-15-01-3 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 312-15-04-6 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 312-16-01-4 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 312-16-05-6 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 322-17-01-5 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 322-17-05-9 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 322-17-20-24 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 322-17-25-30 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 322-17-10-13 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 322-17-14-19 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 331-18-01-2 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 332-19-01-4 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 332-19-05-9 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 332-20-01-3 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 332-20-04-6 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 332-31-01-4 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 411-22-01-5, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 411-23-01-4 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- West Side Social Setting Detox Program Application, 1977 (Box 45.1, Folder 1)
  Includes Social Security Numbers
- Bethesda Mental Health Center - Grant Application, 1983 (Box 45.1, Folder 2)
- Bureau for Health Services - Grant Application, 1978 (Box 45.1, Folder 3)
- Center for Research on Utilization of Scientific Knowledge - Grant Application, 1983 (Box 45.1, Folder 4)
- Community Mental Health Council - Grant Follow-up, 1984 (Box 45.1, Folder 5)
- Corporate Headquarters Alcoholism Project (CHAP) - Grant Renewal, 1976 (Box 45.1, Folder 6)
- Institute for Social Analysis - Grant Application, 1984 (Box 45.1, Folder 7)
- International Law Enforcement Stress Association - Program Grant Application, 1979 (Box 45.1, Folder 8)
- National Institute on Alcohol Abuse - Grant Review, 1979 (Box 45.1, Folder 9)
- National Survey of Occupational Program - Grant Application and Review, 1978 (Box 45.1, Folder 10)
- Trade, Professional and Labor Organizations Occupational Alcoholism Project - Grant Application, 1979 (Box 45.1, Folder 11)
- Valley Forge Medical Foundation Alcohol Project - Grant Application, 1977 (Box 45.1, Folder 12)
- Valley Forge Medical Foundation - Grant Application (1980) (Box 45.1, Folder 13)
- Vera Institute Of Justice (Alcohol Detox Programs) - Grant Application, 1981 (Box 45.1, Folder 14)
- California Bar Association - Grant Application and Renewal, 1976 (Box 45.1, Folder 15)
- EAP Central Connecticut Region Grant Application Addenda, 1979 (Box 45.1, Folder 16)
- EAP Central Connecticut Region Project Description and Grant Proposal, 1979 (Box 45.1, Folder 17)
- Highline School District EAP (Seattle, Washington) - Grant Application, 1979 (Box 45.1, Folder 18)
- Lincoln, Nebraska Council on Alcoholism - EAP Grant Application (Box 45.1, Folder 19)
- Massachusetts Health Policy Institute - Grant Application, 1983 (Box 45.1, Folder 20)
- National Association of State Alcohol and Drug Abuse Directors - HMT Review, 1980 (Box 45.1, Folder 21)
- New Mexico State Occupational Program Services - Grant Application, 1978 (Box 45.1, Folder 22)
- New Orleans Police Department Occupational Alcoholism - Project Grant, 1981 (Box 45.1, Folder 23)
- North Carolina Occupational Alcohol Program - Grant Application Sections IV-VI, 1977-1978 (Box 45.1, Folder 24)
- North Carolina Occupational Alcoholism Program - Grant Application Sections I-III, 1977-1978 (Box 45.1, Folder 25)
- North Carolina Occupational Alcoholism Program - Grant Application Section VII, 1977-1978 (Box 45.1, Folder 26)
- North Carolina Occupational Alcoholism Program - Grant Application Section VI, 1977-1978 (Box 45.1, Folder 27)
- North Carolina Occupational Alcoholism Program - Project Description and Summary (Box 45.1, Folder 28)
- Ohio Tri-County EAP - Grant Application, 1983 (Box 45.1, Folder 29)
- Rhode Island Group Health Association Occupational Alcohol Program - Grant Application and Review, 1977 (Box 45.1, Folder 30)
- Texas Commission on Alcoholism - Grant Application, 1977 (Box 45.1, Folder 31)
- Vermont Statewide EAP - Project Summary (Box 45.1, Folder 32)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 412-25-13-16 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 412-25-08-12 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 412-25-02-07, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 412-26-01-5 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 412-26-06-8 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 412-27-01-4 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 412-27-05-6 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 421-28-01-3 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 422-29-01-5 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 422-29-06-9 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 422-29-10-13 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 422-30-10-13 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Policy Implementation in the Public Sector - Supervisor Interviews 422-30-14-17 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Cornell University/Harrison M. Trice (HMT) - Grant Application, 1985 (Box 46.1, Folder 1)
- Health Policy Institute, Boston University - Grant Application, 1983 (Box 46.1, Folder 2)